(through static):
I didn't understand your e-mail.
(Sheldon:)Uh, can you repeat that?
You're breaking up.
(Amy(on Skype):)I didn't understand your e-mail.
(Sheldon:)Ah. Yeah, I had to get
a little creative
(Sheldon:)because the S, R and M keys
on my laptop stopped working.
"Deaw Aby,
could you pleathe dwive be
(Amy:)to the twain thtow
thubtibe tobowow?"
(Sheldon:)So, is that a yes?
(Amy:)Sheldon, why don't you get
a new computer?
(Amy:)You know that one's out-of-date.
(Sheldon:)Oh, but I like this computer.
(Amy:)The video is failing,
and the sound is cutting out.
(Sheldon:)I'm sorry, I didn't get that.
(through static):
The video is failing,
(Amy:)and the sound is cutting out.
I'm sorry, one more time.
The sound is cutting out.
I can't read that!
The video is failing!
(through static):
Get a new computer.
(Sheldon:)What?
(through static):
Get a new computer.
What?!
(phone rings)
(Sheldon:)Hello?
Get a new computer!
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪